[
    {
        "Question": "What can TACC users use MATLAB for?",
        "Answer Given": "non-commercial, academic use",
        "Score": 0.49325111508369446,
        "Actual Answer": "only for non-commercial, academic purposes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I load MATLAB?",
        "Answer Given": "MATLAB Desktop UI",
        "Score": 0.3926929235458374,
        "Actual Answer": "module load matlab"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Should I launch MATLAB jobs on login nodes?",
        "Answer Given": "Do NOT launch MATLAB on the login nodes",
        "Score": 0.28829994797706604,
        "Actual Answer": "Do NOT launch MATLAB on the login nodes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Where can I submit my MATLAB jobs?",
        "Answer Given": "Slurm scheduler",
        "Score": 0.43189674615859985,
        "Actual Answer": "on the TACC resources, e.g. Frontera, Stampede3, or Lonestar6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Why can I not use MATLAB on login nodes?",
        "Answer Given": "it will prevent other users from doing their work",
        "Score": 0.033072661608457565,
        "Actual Answer": "This may fail and, more importantly, it will prevent other users from doing their work, as your execution will take up too many cycles on the shared login node"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I invoke MATLAB?",
        "Answer Given": "by loading the MATLAB module",
        "Score": 0.08342941105365753,
        "Actual Answer": "matlab"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the command to invoke MATLAB?",
        "Answer Given": "ver",
        "Score": 0.045293401926755905,
        "Actual Answer": "matlab"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the standard way to submit a Slurm job?",
        "Answer Given": "scheduler",
        "Score": 0.0031234289053827524,
        "Actual Answer": "sbatch myjobscript"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I submit a Slurm job?",
        "Answer Given": "in the standard way",
        "Score": 0.030789189040660858,
        "Actual Answer": "sbatch myjobscript"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How is using login nodes for MATLAB jobs system abuse?",
        "Answer Given": "will be treated as such",
        "Score": 0.1337115466594696,
        "Actual Answer": "it will prevent other users from doing their work, as your execution will take up too many cycles on the shared login node"
    }
]